

Asir Intesar Ibne Zaman

I am a positive and diligent individual with strong organizational skills and interpersonal abilities. As a passionate data-driven product enthusiast, I excel at collecting, validating, and modeling datasets to optimize product performance. I have a knack for market research, feature analysis, and identifying valuable patterns. With a strong belief in the power of determination, I continuously strive for professional growth and on my career objectives.







+880 1953608315 M asirintesar97@gmail.com mww.linkedin.com/in/asirintesar # https://asirintesar.github.io



Work Experience

Associate Product Manager (Feb 2024 - Present) **Myalice**

- Developed product roadmaps to prioritize and manage Conducted feature analysis and drafted PRD to drive product development initiatives.
- Maintained sprint plan and release log to keep product
 Fostered cross-functional collaboration among growth visible to stakeholders.
- concrete product growth.
 - engineering, success, and marketing teams.

Product Analyst, Sr. Executive (Oct 2022 - April 2024) **Bdjobs.com Limited**

- Analyzed customer feedback and identified trends to inform product strategy decisions.
- Generated reports on key performance indicators to measure success of current products.
- Analyzed customer feedback and identified trends to inform product strategy decisions.
- Facilitated cross-functional collaboration between engineering, and sales team.

Product Executive (Jan 2022 - Sep 2022) **Adplay Technology Limited**

- Prepared monthly reports highlighting key accomplishments and areas needing improvement.
- Coordinated with internal stakeholders to launch products within specified timelines.
- Drafted detailed business plans outlining financial projections, marketing strategy and pricing models.
- Performed quality assurance tests on all products prior to release into the market place.

Operation Analyst (Internship) (Oct 2021- Jan 2022) Shopup

- Analyzed data to identify operational trends, issues, and
 Collaborated with team to formulate compelling, improvement opportunities.
 - data-driven solutions to operational issues.

Skill & Expertise

Tools & Technologies: Jira, Google Analytics, Mixpanel, Google Data Studio, PowerBI, Tableau, Adobe XD, Figma.

Industrial Knowledge: Product Management, Data Analysis, UIUX Design, Machine Learning, Agile Methodolies.

Language & Database: Python, R, MySQL, MS Sql Server, Bigquery.

Soft Skills & Others: Leadership, Prioritization, Feature Analysis, User Acceptance Testing, Product Requirement Doc.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science & Engineering

American International University - Bangladesh (AIUB)

Jan 2018 - Sep 2021

Awards & Honors:

· Nominated for Best Thesis Award

Extracurricular Activities:

Photographer and Event Organizer at AIUB Photography Club

HSC in Science

Dhaka City College

2014-2016

SSC in Science

Motijheel Govt Boys' High School

2005-2014

Awards & Honors:

Finalist, MGBHS Photography Contest

Training & Certification

- · Product Management Career Track | Bohubrihi
- Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate | Coursera
- · Emotional Intelligence | Bohubrihi

Personal Interest

- Travelling | Travel vlog on youtube channel
- Cycling | Got souvenir from bdcyclist
- Blogging | Writing blogs on data at Medium and LinkedIn, mostly sports
- Aquascaping | Experienced in Planted and Community tank

Reference

Shafi Mohammad Wasif Osman

GM, CLM Innovation & Analytics Robi Axiata Limited

Email: smwosman@gmail.com

Raphael Elvis Rozario

Engineering Lead Myalice

Email: raphael@myalice.ai